So I want to pass in a color into the word adapter so
我希望向 WordAdapter 中传入一个颜色
all the words in that category have the same background color.
使该类别中的所有单词都具有相同的背景颜色
So to do this I will need to modify the word adapter to hold our color
为此 我需要修改 WordAdapter 以便存储我们的
resource value.
颜色资源值
And now I'll need a modifier existing constructor to accept this new
现在我需要修改现有的构造函数 使其接受
color resource ID as an input, and now I need to set the value of m color
这一新的 colorResourceId 并作为输入值
resource ID to be whatever input was passed in as the color resource ID.
现在我需要将 mColorResourceId 的值设为 colorResourceId 传入的值
And then at the bottom of the give you method I need to set the color.
然后在 getView 方法的底部 我需要设置该颜色
So that's done with this block of code here.
这段代码就完成了
So first I'm setting the theme of the color for
首先设置列表项的主题背景颜色
the lists item and then I'm finding he color that the resource ID maps to and
然后找到该资源 ID 对应的颜色
then finally set in the background color of the text container view.
最后设置文本容器视图的背景颜色
I know colors can be a bit tricky and
我知道颜色比较难设置
it did take me a couple tries to get this right.
我也是试了好几次才设置正确
But follow along and you'll be able to do something similar in your own app.
但是一步步跟着操作 你将能够在自己的应用中达到类似的效果
So now, we need a convert the color resource ID into a color value.
现在 我们需要将 colorResourceId 转换为颜色值
To do this, let's head on over to the list item way out.
为此 我们转到 list_item 布局
In here we need to make sure that the linear layout in the list item layout
在这里 我们需要确保 list_item 布局中的 LinearLayout
has an ID on the container.
在容器中具有 ID
So back to the word adapter.
回到 WordAdapter
So now that we have the word adapter constructor set up to take in the color
现在我们已经将 WordAdapter 构造函数设为接受 colorResourceId
resource ID, we need to modify the other activities so
我们需要修改其他 Activity
that when we call the word adopt a constructor.
这样 当我们调用 WordAdopter 构造函数时
We're passing the right inputs.
我们传入的是正确的输入值
So we that here in the numbers activity.
打开 NumbersActivity 并转到这里
I want to add that here in the colors activity, and similarly for
在 ColorsActivity 中的此处也添加下
the phrases activity and lastly for the family activity.
PhrasesActivity 也执行类似的操作 最后是 FamilyActivity
And one more thing before I forget.
差点忘了提醒一件事
So back on the list item layout, remember to remove the background color
回到 list_item 布局 别忘了删掉我们硬编码到
that we hard coded into list item layout.
list_item 布局中的背景颜色
So we had set it to always appear as an orange background color behind the text,
我们将其设为了始终在文字后面显示为橘色背景颜色
but now that we can set the color dynamically when the list items created
但现在我们可以在创建列表项后 动态设置该颜色
we don't need it any more.
因此不再需要这行代码
So let's test out the app now.
现在测试下我们的应用吧
So let's start with numbers.
先从 Numbers 开始
All right orange is expected and then family members, whoa.
是预期的橘色 然后看看 FamilyMembers
That looks really good.
哇 看起来很不错
So going back to the colors nice and
返回并进入 Colors 类别 不错
then lastly phrases while liking that blue.
最后进入 Phrases 哇 喜欢这个蓝色
So each category shows a different color as expected and it's all coming together
每个类别都如预期地显示不同的颜色 一切都更改完毕
and looking really polished now, so high five on that great job.
看起来很美观 完成的非常棒！